

 export const CardStock = [
    
    { id:1,  color: '#ffcc00', colorBack: '#fc993c', front:'T', back:"U",  answer: 'T'},
    { id:2,  color: '#ff6666', colorBack: '#e3670c' , front:'S', back:"T", answer: 'T'},
    { id:3,  color: '#323edd', colorBack: '#a1d76f', front:'E', back:"R", answer: 'R'},
    { id:4,  color: '#66cccc', colorBack: '#a1d76f', front:'W', back:"T", answer: 'W'},
    { id:5,  color: '#1fe5bd', colorBack: '#f40968' , front:'A', back:"H", answer: 'A'},
    { id:6,  color: '#41a7b3', colorBack: '#f3e94c', front:'E', back:"C", answer: 'C'},
    { id:7,  color: '#ca431d', colorBack: '#2ca4bf', front:'H', back:"F", answer: 'H'},
    { id:8,  color: '#3a0088', colorBack: '#d4abdc', front:'O', back:"I", answer: 'I'},
    { id:9,  color: '#00454a', colorBack: '#50cb86', front:'R', back:"L", answer: 'L'},
    { id:10,  color: '#f66767', colorBack: '#323edd', front:'S', back:"K", answer: 'S'},
    { id:11,  color: '#57acc5', colorBack: '#fbb448', front:'Y', back:"S", answer: 'Y'},
    { id:12,  color: '#e8f044', colorBack: '#726a95', front:'T', back:"!", answer: 'T'},
]

